export const cities = [
  {
    country: "Austria",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Vienna",
        answer:
          "The city of grand palaces and museums, the home of Opera and Beethoven, Vienna is a city steeped in culture and grandeur.A walk down the city’s beautiful Ringstrasse Boulevard, lined with royal buildings like the Hofburg Imperial Palace and many beautiful parks, is a great way to let the magic of Vienna grow on you. The opulent Schonbrunn & Belvedere Palaces and the ornate St Stephen’s Cathedral are architectural marvels and a must - visit for art and history enthusiasts.Don’t forget to sip the famous Viennese coffee at one of many cozy coffee houses and gaze in wonder at the world famous Vienna Opera House.",
      },
      {
        question: "Salzburg",
        answer:
          "A charming city surrounded by rolling green meadows, majestic historical buildings and it is the birthplace of genius composer Mozart. The old town with its stunning baroque buildings is a UNESCO World Heritage Site, while the imposing Hohensalzburg fortress boasts of being Europe’s last preserved castle.The grand extravaganza of culture, music and the arts, the Salzburger Festspiele during summers is an experience to remember.",
      },
      {
        question: "Graz",
        answer:
          "Austria’s second largest city with six universities and one of Europe’s best preserved Old town areas, Graz has much to offer.There are numerous museums, impressive baroque & renaissance style buildings and a unique forested hill in the centre of the city offering panoramic views as well.",
      },
      {
        question: "Innsbruck",
        answer:
          "The idyllic alpine town surrounded by high mountains has plenty of options. You could enjoy a leisurely walk through the old town and marvel at the glittering Goldenes Dachl adorned with more than 2500 shiny tiles or get a peek into the Tyrolean Folk Art Museum, one of the finest museums for regional heritage in Europe. Innsbruck has world renowned ski resorts which can be enjoyed in the winter months.Adventure enthusiasts can go hiking up the gorgeous meadows, bungee jumping at Europa Bridge, or take the thrilling funicular ride up the Nordkette mountain range.",
      },
      {
        question: "Bregenz",
        answer:
          "Located on the Eastern edge of Lake Constance, Bregenz offers sweeping views of the Swiss and German Alps. Stroll around the beautiful promenade by the lake or take a cable car up the Pfander Mountain for breathtaking vistas of the Lake Constance. The mountain top is also a great place to relish a lunch with spectacular views or meander along a hiking trail.Get bowled over by the opera and orchestras at the annual Bregenz festival(July- August) performed at the floating lakeside platform. The architecture, history and art legacy of the city can be admired in museums and beautiful buildings across the town.",
      },
      {
        question: "Wachau",
        answer:
          "Flanking the beautiful Danube River, this rich valley is one of the best South Austria tourist attractions.A UNESCO World heritage site for its cultural significance and unmatched natural splendour, Wachau valley is popular amidst wine connoisseurs for some of the best white wines in the world. Studded with some magnificent monasteries(like the baroque Melk monastery) castles and fortresses Wachau valley offers lots of history and architectural delights too, this spot worth a visit.",
      },
      {
        question: "Hallstatt & Salzkammergut",
        answer:
          "This picturesque resort area near Salzburg offers the quintessential Austrian experience, with shimmering blue lakes(76 lakes in all!), stunning alpine ranges, charming villages, and luxurious spa towns.Situated by the Lake Hallstatt and included on UNESCO’s world heritage sites list is the fairy tale village Hallstatt which happens to be heavily overcrowded by tourists(be aware!). Undoubtedly one of the most beautiful places to see in Austria, Halstatt’s stunning pastel colored houses, underground salt lake Salzwelten and Ice Cave on Dachstein Mountain will take your breath away.The spa town of Bad Ischl and the romantic St Wolfgang are other tourist favorites, yet expensive.",
      },
      {
        question: "Wörthersee",
        answer:
          "Canoeing, spelunking, pretty churches and the hometown of Porsche are reason enough to spend a few days at Austria’s favoured summer destination.The beautiful Worthersee Lake offers ample opportunities for swimming, boating and canoeing in the summer months. You can head to the colourful Griffen Stalactite cave for some thrill and exploration. Admiring the 12th century ancient Cathedral of Gurk and a visit to Gmund the birthplace of Porsche complete your list of must-do experiences.",
      },
      {
        question: "Grossglockner High Alpine Road",
        answer:
          "If you are fond of road trips, then put Grossglockner High Alpine Road on your bucket list.The hairpin road passes through lush alpine meadows, snowfields, and daunting cliffs.The road is literally your gateway to escape into nature.You will find a number of vantage points along the road to admire the raw and breathtaking beauty of Austria.",
      },
      {
        question: "National Park Hohe Tauern",
        answer:
          "National Park Hohe Tauern is one of the oldest and largest national parks in Austria. You can find the country's largest mountains, glaciers, and forests in this national park.Spot beautiful and unique animal species.You could either explore the park on your own or join a tour guided by the park ranger.",
      },
      {
        question: "The Alps",
        answer:
          "Dominating the western part of Austria’s landscape, the alps are worth a visit for nature lovers all year round.From hikes to alpine climbing various outdoor activities can be performed during spring and summer time.Not to forget every kind of skiing during winter.",
      },
      {
        question: "Schrems",
        answer:
          "One of the hidden gems of Austria, this city offers a lot of extraordinary sights.Not only is the brewery of the world famous ‘Schremser’ beer as well as the manufacturing facilities of the unique ‘Waldviertler’ shoes located in the city center. Nearby there is also a local art museum run by greek immigrant Varlamis.The surrounding hiking paths providing marvellous views of the landscape and even lead through a moor, make this remote town more than worth the travel effort.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Belgium",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Brussels",
        answer:
          "The atomium, Manneken-Pis, Royal Palace, Arc de Triomphe and the Jubelpark, Grand Place",
      },
      {
        question: "Antwerp",
        answer:
          "The cathedral, the historical city centre, MAS museum, Central Station",
      },
      {
        question: "Bruges",
        answer: "The historical city centre, Belfort, Historium",
      },
      {
        question: "Ghent",
        answer:
          "The castle (Gravensteen), the cathedral, the historical city centre",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Bosnia-and-Herzegovina",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Sarajevo",
        answer: "The capital city of Bosnia and Herzegovina has a unique mix of traditional charms and modern influences. Within a few minutes’ walk you can find the Catholic cathedral, the Orthodox cathedral, the mosque, and the synagogue. The city and its population suffered grave humanitarian crisis during the ‘Siege of Sarajevo’ for three difficult years during the Balkan Wars of the 1990s. Today, the bullet holes arecovered and debris have disappeared and instead cafes, restaurants, lodges, guest houses and art galleries have sprung up amidst the Ottoman and Austro-Hungarian heritage buildings. The city is often credited as being the flash point of starting the devastating World War I. Very few cities in the world can offer such a variety of interesting things in such a small area as Sarajevo does. Historical attractions, natural beauty and unique experience of a place where „East meets West“ are all reasons which attract and continue to bring so many visitors to Sarajevo. Winter offers plenty of opportunities for winter sports and recreation in the snow. Spring and autumn, with their mild climate offer opportunities for pleasant exploration of natural beauty of the outskirts and a vibrant programme of cultural events in the city. Summer is a time when the city, its squares and streets become an on-the-go holiday; it is the time when the city lives twenty-four seven. Sarajevo has its own specific gravity, so a single visit very often becomes the start of a more permanent attachment to this city and its people. So the best thing to do is to visit because we’d like to hear if you fell in love with Sarajevo too! *Landmarks: Baščaršija (Old Town), Gazi Husrevbeg’s Mosque, Spring of Bosnia river…",
      },
      {
        question: "Banja Luka",
        answer: "Banja Luka is the administrative capital of the Republika Srpska, the second largest city in Bosnia. Roman trade route from Salona to Servitium passed through it. To protect this route (and to enjoy the healing water springs they had discovered in the area) the Romans built a fortress here, the walls of which encompassed an entire miniature town. When the Roman Empire collapsed, the Slavs took over. Once the Ottomans finally controlled the town, they gave it a distinct oriental flavor. The Ottoman governor for Bosnia had his headquarters here for a while, building bridges and mills, and in its Ottoman glory days the town had some 40 mosques. In the course of the Ottoman centuries, Banja Luka was destroyed repeatedly by Ottoman-Austrian warfare (as well as earthquakes and plagues) until eventually the Austrian-Hungarian Empire absorbed Banja Luka peacefully in the 19th century. They rapidly modernized the town, building factories and connecting it to Vienna and other capital cities. The town expanded tremendously in the 20th century. *Landmarks: Kastel fortress, Ferhadija Mosque, Cathedral of Christ the Saviour, Banj Hill…",
      },
      {
        question: "Mostar",
        answer: "Mostar is the chief city and, historically, the capital of Herzegovina. It is situated in mountainous country along the Neretva River and lies on the Sarajevo-Ploče rail line. First mentioned in 1452, Mostar became a Turkish garrison town in the 16th century. In 1566 the Turks replaced the town’s wooden suspension bridge over the Neretva with a stone arch one, hence the name Mostar (from Serbo-Croatian most, “bridge”). This stone bridge had a single arch 90 feet (27 metres) wide and was a masterpiece of Ottoman engineering. In November 1993, during the Bosnian civil war, the bridge was destroyed by artillery fire from Bosnian Croat forces. A major rebuilding project was undertaken to restore the bridge and nearby buildings that had also been damaged; the bridge reopened in 2004. The bridge and the surrounding area were added to UNESCO’s World Heritage list in 2005.",
      },
      {
        question: "Trebinje",
        answer: "By far the prettiest city in Republika Srpska, Trebinje has a compact centre with a tiny walled Old Town flanked by a leafy market square. The Trebišnjica River is slow and shallow as it passes through, its banks lined with swimming spots and replicas of waterwheels which were once used for irrigation. Mountains provide a sun-baked backdrop, while hills topped with Orthodox churches punctuate the suburbs."
      },
      {
        question: "Jajce",
        answer: "A historical gem, with a highly evocative walled Old Town clinging to a steep rocky knoll with rivers on two sides. The Pliva River tumbles into the Vrbas River by way of an impressive urban waterfallright at the very foot of the town walls. Immediately to the west, the Pliva is dammed to form two pretty lakes which are popular with swimmers, strollers, bikers and boaters"
      },
      {
        question: "Kravica Waterfall",
        answer: "An unreal Disney-esque quality to this outstanding natural attraction, where the Trebižat River plummets in a broad 25m-high arc into an emerald pool. In spring, this gorgeous mini-Niagara pounds itself into a dramatic, steamy fury. In summer it's a more gentle cascade, but the basin offers an idyllic respite from the sweltering heat for hundreds of locals and tourists"
      },
      {
        question: "Epic Yugoslav monument - Tjentište",
        answer: "Memorial in Sutjeska National Park"
      }
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Croatia",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Osijek",
        answer:
          "most famous parts are the part of the old town called Tvrđa, which was built as a baroque town in 18th century.",
      },
      {
        question: "Šibenik",
        answer:
          "on the UNESCO World Heritage List; there are four old fortresses for visitors to take a look at",
      },
      {
        question: "Dubrovnik",
        answer:
          "‘The Pearl of the Adriatic'; Dubrovnik gained its popularity amongst Hollywood movie industry",
      },
      {
        question: "Zadar",
        answer:
          "a central old town is made out of Roman ruins and old churches",
      },
      {
        question: "Rovinj",
        answer:
          "a city with Venetian architecture; The Amarin and Skaraba beaches are one of the best to visit",
      },
      {
        question: "Pula",
        answer:
          "the largest city in Istria County; ancient Roman buildings, the most famous of which is the Pula Arena",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Czech-Republic",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Prague",
        answer:
          "Prague castle (largest castle in the world), Oldtown, Charles bridge",
      },
      {
        question: "Karlovy Vary",
        answer: "Old town, Film festival",
      },
      {
        question: "Český Krumlov",
        answer: "Old town",
      },
      {
        question: "Brno",
        answer: "Old town, Cathedra",
      },
      {
        question: "Ostrava",
        answer: "Lower Vítkovice",
      },
      {
        question: "Pilsen",
        answer: "Breweries, Oldtown, Cathedral",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "France",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Paris",
        answer:
          "Tour Eiffel, Arc de Triomphe, Basilique Montmartre, Sacré-cœur, avenue des Champs-Elysées",
      },
      {
        question: "Marseille",
        answer:
          "quartier du Panier (very typical district in the city center), vieux-port (old port), palais Longchamp (palace with its gardens), Mucem museum & Fort Saint Jean (near the sea, you can go to the terrace of the museum (free access) and you cross the sea on a bridge directly to join the Fort Saint Jean), Basilique Notre-Dame-de-la-Garde",
      },
      {
        question: "Lyon",
        answer:
          "Old town of Lyon, Basilique de Fourvière, Place des Terreaux (where bars are), La Part Dieu shopping mall, Croix-Rousse district (historical district and “traboules”, small streets very typical from Lyon), quartier des murs peints (district of the painted walls)",
      },
      {
        question: "Bordeaux",
        answer:
          "walk along the quays, palais Gallien, cathédrale Sainte Andrée, Place Gambetta, Basilique Saint Michel, Grand Théâtre, la porte Cailhau (Cailhau’s gate), marché des Capucins (food market)",
      },
      {
        question: "Annecy",
        answer:
          "old town called “Vieille ville” (don’t mix up with “Annecy le Vieux”, a city nearby Annecy), lake of Annecy with its Love Bridge (Pont des Amours) and walk along the Europe’s gardens (Jardins de l’Europe), Palais de l’Île",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Germany",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Berlin",
        answer:
          "the capital of Germany; was divided in East and West Berlin for almost 30 years by the Berlin Wall",
      },
      {
        question: "Cologne (Köln)",
        answer: "a carnival in February; has Europe’s third highest cathedral",
      },
      {
        question: "Dresden",
        answer:
          "it's called Florence on the Elbe; there are free walking tours around the oldtown (offered in English, German, Spanish)",
      },
      {
        question: "Hamburg",
        answer:
          "home to Germany’s largest miniature railroad exhibition; The “Reeperbahn” is the famous party-area and red-light district of Hamburg",
      },
      {
        question: "Munich (München)",
        answer:
          "home to Octoberfest (Wiesn) which is a 16-18 day folk festival featuring beer tents (up to 6000 people per tent) and fair rides",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Hungary",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Debrecen",
        answer:
          "Hungary's second largest city after Budapest; the largest Hungarian city in the 18th century",
      },
      {
        question: "Győr",
        answer:
          "halfway between Budapest and Vienna – situated on one of the important roads of Central Europe.",
      },
      {
        question: "Pécs",
        answer:
          "the administrative and economic center of Baranya County; the seat of the Roman Catholic Diocese of Pécs",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Macedonia",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Skopje",
        answer:
          "Europe’s most eclectic capital city. Efforts have been made to infuse new culture in the form of museums, fountains, bridges, and statuary throughout the city.",
      },
      {
        question: "Bitola",
        answer:
          " an old Ottoman town once known as the “City of Consuls” because it served as a diplomatic center for the region; you can see colorful townhouses from the 18th century",
      },
      {
        question: "Kruševo",
        answer:
          "Although it only has 10,000 citizens, it was once its own republic, in the centuries-long struggle to win independence from the Ottoman Empire",
      },
      {
        question: "Ohrid",
        answer:
          "It has a remarkable history and heritage to share; At the top of the list are the frescoes inside Saint Sofia Church, the Ancient Theatre, St. Clement Church (13th century), and Tsar Samuil’s fortress",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Malta",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Valletta",
        answer:
          "The capital city of Malta and the capital city of European Culture in 2018; a medieval city of which, many parts have just been refurbished so it’s looking fantastic. This city is packed with monuments and historic buildings everywhere.",
      },
      {
        question: "Birgu",
        answer:
          "the prettiest of the old 3 cities just opposite Valletta; it was the old seating point of the Knights of St. John before Valletta was built",
      },
      {
        question: "Rabat",
        answer:
          "it is the highest city on the island and you can visit catacombs there and have viewing points of the island",
      },
      {
        question: "Mdina",
        answer:
          "situated inside Rabat. This was the old capital of Malta and is concentrated in every corner with history. There is a Cathedral you can visit there. The streets in Mdina are very narrow and fun explore.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Norway",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Oslo",
        answer:
          "It is recommended to walk down it’s main street, Karl Johans Gate, starting at the King’s Palace (open for the tourists during the summer) at the Slottsparken and ending at the Opera and Barcode buildings known for its unique architectural design in Oslo. Neat the Opera, there is also Akershus Festning free of charge.",
      },
      {
        question: "Bergen",
        answer:
          "Bergen is the second biggest city in Norway. It’s known for its 7 mountains and rainy weather. Ulriken is the tallest mountain around Bergen and it’s 643 m above sea level.",
      },
      {
        question: "Stavanger",
        answer:
          " surrounded by beautiful fjords, mountains and long white beaches. Being Norway’s oil and energy capital, the city attracts different nationalities and can offer an urban and lively atmosphere along with its scenic landmarks.",
      },
      {
        question: "Trondheim",
        answer:
          "The 3rd biggest city in Norway and a home for 30 000 students. They shape the culture of the city by arranging many activities. If you want to taste a bit of a student life, visit the restaurant at the Samfunnet, driven by the students, where all the employees starting from the chef to the waitress are volunteering students. The food is tremendous.",
      },
      {
        question: "Tromsø",
        answer:
          "A city in the northern Norway popular for the northern lights.  The Fjellheisen (funicular) will lift you up 371 meters for 4 minutes to the orchestra place to see Tromsø in panorama. Here you can enjoy a spectacular view of Tromsø, with an almost endless view of islands, fjords, mountains and sea. If you turn the other way, you will see the majestic Tromsdalstinden which towers 1,238 meters above sea level.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Poland",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Warsaw",
        answer:
          "Capital city of Poland, you should see there Palace of Culture and Science, Belweder Palace and Wilanow Palace.",
      },
      {
        question: "Krakow",
        answer:
          "Former capitals of Poland.  You should visit Wawel Castel and grab a coffee at beautiful square.",
      },
      {
        question: "Wroclaw",
        answer:
          " One of the favorite cities amongst young poles. Can you find all dwarves hidden in the city?",
      },
      {
        question: "Łódź",
        answer: "City full of history, museums and theaters",
      },
      {
        question: "Poznań",
        answer:
          "a city with very colorful and charming square, you should try a famous St. Martin croissant while visiting.",
      },
      {
        question: "Tricity",
        answer:
          "If you want to see beautiful oldtown, swim in the sea, and party the same very day this is place for you.",
      },
      {
        question: "Zakopane",
        answer:
          "Nestled at the foothills of the Tatra Mountains, Zakopane is a popular destination for outdoor enthusiasts. In addition to hiking and skiing opportunities, the town is known for its unique wooden architecture and vibrant folk culture.",
      },
      {
        question: "Tatra Mountains",
        answer:
          "It is a mountain range that forms a natural border between Slovakia and Poland. They are the highest mountain range in the Carpathian Mountains Bieszczady Mountains - is a mountain range that runs from the extreme south-east of Poland and north-east of Slovakia through to western Ukraine. Great place to take a brake from civilization",
      },
      {
        question: "Baltic Sea",
        answer:
          "Shaped like a crocodile Mediterranean Sea of Atlantic. Beautiful coast line with sandy beaches and beautiful dunes.",
      },
      { 
        question: "Mazury",
        answer:
          "Great place in northwestern part of Poland full of lakes and forests",
      },
      {
        question: "Słowiński National Park",
        answer:
          " Situated along the Baltic coast, Słowiński National Park is known for its shifting sand dunes, which create a unique and ever-changing landscape. The park also encompasses Lake Łebsko and Lake Gardno, providing habitats for various bird species",
      },
      {
        question: "Hel Peninsula",
        answer:
          "Jutting out into the Baltic Sea, the Hel Peninsula offers picturesque beaches, sand dunes, and opportunities for water sports such as windsurfing and kitesurfing. It's also known for its fishing villages and fresh seafood.",
      },
      {
        question: "Białowieża Forest",
        answer:
          "Located on the border between Poland and Belarus, Białowieża, Forest is one of the last and largest remaining parts of the immense primeval forest that once stretched across the European Plain. It's a UNESCO World Heritage site and home to the European bison, as well as diverse flora and fauna.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Slovakia",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Bratislava",
        answer:
          "Bratislava is the only capital in the world that borders two independent countries. Bratislava castle or Slovak Radio is are two of many places you should visit there.",
      },
      {
        question: "Košice",
        answer:
          "Košice is the second largest city in Slovakia. The city center consists of historic buildings such as the most famous one - St. Elizabeth Cathedral",
      },
      {
        question: "Bardejov",
        answer:
          "The town of Bardejov is a historically and culturally rich town, considered one of the most beautiful Slovak towns. The historical center of Bardejov, together with the complex of buildings forming the Jewish suburb from the beginning of the 18th century, was inscribed on the list in 2000 - the UNESCO World Cultural and Natural Heritage.",
      },
      {
        question: "Trenčín",
        answer:
          "Trenčín is one of the three oldest Slovak cities. The city includes Trenčín Castle and various other interesting monuments.",
      },
      {
        question: "Prešov",
        answer:
          "The city of Prešov is the third largest. In addition to the historic center, the most important salt deposit is the Solivar part with a number of preserved technical monuments related to salt mining. There are several castle ruins around the city.",
      },
      {
        question: "Banská Štiavnica",
        answer:
          "Banská Štiavnica, located in central Slovakia, is a city included in the UNESCO World Heritage List. The former mining town is one of the most beautiful and historically most interesting towns in Slovakia.",
      },
      {
        question: "Trnava",
        answer:
          "The oldest free royal borough TRNAVA was the Church 'capital' of the Kingdom of Hungary for several centuries in the past. Only a few towns of central Europe can boast such a large section of town walls. For their high level of preservation, Trnava town walls are unique from the construction point of view and rank among the most significant monuments of the kind in Europe.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Slovenia",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Ljubljana",
        answer:
          "capital city of Slovenia - also a city of dragons, which are depicted on the city’s coat of arms and the famous Dragon Bridge is adorned with four dragon statues; the most important landmark is the Ljubljana Castle",
      },
      {
        question: "Bled",
        answer:
          "This city is a symbol of Slovenia’s beauty. It is known for its idyllic Alpine lake with a small island located in the center. The island has a small church and there are many legends connected to this place. The lake is surrounded by mountains and you can get a great view from a castle on the cliff next to the lake.",
      },
      {
        question: "Piran",
        answer:
          "a beautiful small medieval city, located next to the Adriatic Sea; overlooking the city is the church of St. George, form where you have great views on the cliffs next to Piran and in nice weather you can even see Italy’s shores",
      },
      {
        question: "Maribor",
        answer:
          "the second largest city in Slovenia and the home to the oldest grape vine in the world; the most beautiful and oldest part of the town – Lent – is located next to the river Drava",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Spain",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Madrid",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Granada",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Sevilla",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Córdoba",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "San Sebastián",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Valencia",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Alicante",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Barcelona ",
        answer: null,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Switzerland",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Zurich",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Lucerne",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Geneva",
        answer: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Lausanne",
        answer: null,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    country: "Sweden",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Stockholm",
        answer:
          " our capital city. Filled with museums, restaurants, and culture! Do not forget to visit the archipelago while you’re there",
      },
      {
        question: "Gothenburg",
        answer:
          "'Sveriges framstjärt'. Speaking of archipelagos Gothenburg also has one and it’s beautiful! Go here in the summer and swim in the beautiful waters.",
      },
    ],
  },
  // {
  //   country: "Tunisia",
  //   cities: [
  //     {
  //       question: "Djerba",
  //       answer:
  //         "Djerba is an island with a picture-perfect beach escape. The island town of Houmt Souk is the main point of interest off the beach, with an old town district that is a muddle of whitewashed houses. Houmt Souk's shopping is an attraction in itself, with plenty of handicraft vendors for browsing and haggling opportunities off the beach.",
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: "Carthage",
  //       answer:
  //         "Once Rome's major rival, Carthage was the city of the seafaring Phoenicians forever memorialized in the Punic Wars. The atmospheric ruins of this ancient town now sit beside the sea amid the suburbs of Tunis, a warning that even the greatest cities can be reduced to rubble.",
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: "Sidi Bou Said",
  //       answer:
  //         "Impossibly cute, and amazingly photogenic, Sidi Bou Said is a clifftop village of petite dimensions that seem to have fallen off an artist's canvas. Unsurprisingly, artists have feted this little hamlet for decades. The whitewashed alleyways, wrought-iron window frames, and colorful blue doors are Tunisian village architecture at their finest, while the Mediterranean backdrop is the cherry on top.",
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: "Sousse",
  //       answer:
  //         "Overlooked by the mighty fortifications of the Ribat and Kasbah, the medina in Sousse just begs to be explored. This lovely old town district is a warren of looping lanes, rimmed by whitewashed houses, and a shopping paradise with a tempting selection of ceramics, leatherwork, and metalwork on display.",
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: "Chott el Djerid",
  //       answer:
  //         "The moonscape surroundings of the Chott el Djerid are a storybook panorama brought to life; filled with shimmering mirages on the horizon and jigsaw puzzle pieces of blindingly white cracked land under foot.",
  //     },
  //     {
  //       question: "Hammamet",
  //       answer:
  //         "Hammamet is all about the beach. This is Tunisia's top sun-and-sea resort; a dreamy place dotted with pristine white buildings set beside a bright blue sea. It's a no stress kind of place that sums up the pleasures of Tunisia in one pretty package.",
  //     },
  //   ],
  // },
  {
    country: "Turkiye",
    cities: [
      {
        question: "Kapadokya",
        answer:
          "The surreal swooping rock valleys of Cappadocia are every photographer's dream. Cliff ridges and hill crests are home to rippling panoramas of wave-like rock or wacky-shaped pinnacles that have been formed by millennia of wind and water action. And if you don't feel like hiking for the views, this is one of the world's top destinations to take a hot air balloon ride.",
      },
      {
        question: "Pamukkale",
        answer:
          "One of Turkey's most famous natural wonders, the pure white travertine terraces of Pamukkale ('Cotton Castle' in English) cascade down the slope looking like an out-of-place snowfield amid the green landscape.",
      },
      {
        question: "Aspendos-Antalya",
        answer:
          "Just south of Antalya, the jaw-dropping mammoth bulk of the Roman Theater of Aspendos celebrates the pomp and ceremony of Marcus Aurelius' rule. Considered the finest surviving example of a classical age theater still standing in the world, it is one of antiquity's star attractions.",
      },
      {
        question: "Ephesus",
        answer:
          "Not to be missed, the mighty ruin of Ephesus is a city of colossal monuments and marble-columned roads. One of the most complete, still-standing Roman cities in the Mediterranean region, this is the place to experience what life must have been like during the golden age of the Roman Empire.",
      },
      {
        question: "Topkapı Palace",
        answer:
          "Sumptuous beyond belief, the Topkapı Palace takes you into the fantastical, opulent world of the sultans. It was from here that the sultans of the Ottoman Era carved out an empire that would extend up into Europe and down through the Middle East and into Africa.",
      },
    ],
  },
];
